ibps-recruitment.in 2016-11-25

# Your privacy is important to us-IBPS Recruitment

Ibps-Recruitment is website created as a resource to help people know about latest recruitment, exams and results, answer key, admit cad etc. The site primarily focused on Government jobs, bank jobs, railway jobs, defence jobs, private jobs, exam results, exam admit card, answer keys, interview, previous question papers, exam syllabus, admissions, entrance exams and more. It intends to be a great platform for job seekers without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the disclaimer policy for www.ibps-recruitment.in

The content provided by www.ibps-recruitment.in is solely for informational purposes only and we hold no right whatsoever for all the activity that a visitor (you) does on other web pages linked from www.ibps-recruitment.in

Since we verify every information at the time of publishing them on ibps-recruitment.in and we (ibps-recruitment.in) can’t be held any response for any type of changes made to original rules, notifications by an organization, institution, bank and department at a later date. It’s your task to ensure and take care of official notifications, announcement by visiting official website.

**Privacy Policy:**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at khalludomains@gmail.com At www.ibps-recruitment.in , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ibps-recruitment.in and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, ibps-recruitment.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Double Click DART Cookie**

Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on www.ibps-recruitment.in  
· Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ibps-recruitment.in. and other sites on the Internet.

· Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ibps-recruitment.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. ibps-recruitment.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.ibps-recruitment.in privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
